elenasmodels.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Elena's Models

Great media Limited (Elena's Models the website) recognize that your privacy is very important and that you have a right to control your personal information. We understand that providing personal information is an act of trust and we strive to protect your personal information and safeguard your privacy.

The following sections set out how we handle and protect your personal information:

  1. ## Information Collection And Use

Great Media Limited (Elena's Models the website) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will NEVER sell, rent, or share this information with any other party; unless it is required for the purposes of providing the service you’re requested. The users are not allowed to sell, share or in any other way distribute the personal contact information of other members of Elena's Models that they receive through Elena's Models. Any contact information a member of Elena's Models that is received through Elena's Models directly from member to member is considered as shared by each party and has not been disclosed by Elena’s Models. No other use of the contact information is allowed. It is not allowed to obtain the contact information via Elena's Models members for any other purpose than starting personal online communication.

The information of members of Elena's Models cannot be used for the means of a media broadcast, unless otherwise is explicitly agreed in writing, and should be treated as private and confidential, including but not limited to photos of Elena's Models members, the personal ads of Elena's Models members, the success stories of Elena's Models members and any other information that the members of Elena's Models shared in confidence with Elena's Models or agreed on being published on Elena's Models website. The publication of such information on Elena's Models does not specify that this information is in the public domain, and should be treated as private and confidential.

Elena's Models will use the Member's email address to send newsletters and promotions with updates regarding the Elena's Models service. The Member may unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time through the newsletter link on the Home Page of their Member's account “Newsletter subscriptions”. An unsubscribe link also appears at the end of each newsletter. Elena's Models may also send its Members offers regarding the products and services of its partners. Members may terminate their Membership with Elena's Models at any time, thus discontinuing any further communication from Elena's Models.

  2. ## Registration

By registering, using or subscribing to the Services, you confirm that you have read and consent to:

    * the collection of your personal information including, for example, your contact information, demographic information, age, gender and dating gender preference), including information from social networking sites. 
    * the processing of your personal information, including your sensitive information (including, for example your dating gender preference, dating relationship experiences, ethnicity, religion) 
    * the sharing of personal information with third parties as described in Section 3 of this Policy. 
    * the storage and processing of your personal information in Hong Kong (and other countries) as described in Section 4 of this Policy. 
    * the use of cookies and similar technologies to store and access information on devices you connect to the Services in accordance with our Cookie Policy. 
    * the use of your personal information to send you Elena’s Models emails, promotions and advertising in accordance with Section 3 and Section 4 of this Policy and 
    * the use of information in identifying your exact location when you have enabled features and functions of the Services that use your device’s location. 
  3. ## Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties

Our Services allow you to share information about yourself with other individuals, including other users and potential users of the Services. Consider your own privacy and personal safety when sharing your information with anyone, including information you share through your profile, as profiles include basic information that was provided at registration, information provided through a Social Networking Site, and may include other information added by you (for example, your religion, ethnicity and physical characteristics), as well as information about your use of the Service (for example, whether you were recently logged in to Elena's Models

Information on your profile is viewable by other users or visitors to our Services, and may also be viewable through public search or on third-party sites that you use. We do not control who reads the information you share or what others may do with this information, so we encourage you to use discretion and caution with respect to your personal information..

We may share information with third parties as follows:

    * with our business partners who offer a service to you jointly with us, for example, when running a contest or promotion.
    * in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party 

We may also share information with others that is not personal information or that is in an aggregated or anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual.

  4. ## Information We Collect

When you register, use or subscribe to any of our Services or take part in any interactive features of the Services (such as any contests, games, promotions, quizzes, surveys, research or other services or features), we may collect a variety of information, including:

    * **Contact Information** such as your name, email address, phone number, including mobile phone number, and correspondence address (“Contact Information”)
    * **Other Information** such as birth date, photographs, videos, password, demographic information, your personal interests and background, gender, age, dating gender preference, physical characteristics, ethnicity, religion, and geographical location (including GPS). We may also receive information (for example, your email address) through other users, for example, if they have tried to refer Elenas Models to you.
    * **Information about you** during conversations between you and our representatives by phone or instant online chat services
    * **Information About How You Use the Elena's Models.** We may collect information about your participation and actions on the Services. This may include information such as the pages and profiles you view, how you browse the Services, purchases you make through the Service. It can also include the various functions and features that you use, such as chat and video chat, the connections you make, other friends or contacts you invite to the Services and profile searches you perform, or your use of our applications.
    * **Information from Content You Upload.** When you upload photos or other content to the Services, we may collect information about the content, such as photo’s or content was taken or uploaded, and how you use them, who views them.
    * **Information Automatically Collected.** When you access our Elenas Models website, we automatically record information from your device and its software, such as your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, platform type, the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave our website, date and time stamp and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. When you access our Services using a mobile device, we may also receive or collect identification numbers associated with your device (such as a UDID), mobile carrier, device type and manufacturer, and, if you have enabled features and functions of the Services that use your device’s location, your geographical location data (including GPS). We also collect information about your usage of, and activity on, our Services. Also, some of the information we collect, for example an IP address, can sometimes be used to approximate a device's location.
    * **Cookies and Similar Technologies.** We may use cookies and similar technologies, including those from third parties, to collect, analyze and store information and to provide and improve the Services.
    * **Your Communications with Us and Other Users.** We collect communications you send to us (such as emails), comments that you post on our blog(s) we have on a third-party service, such as our YouTube, Twitter and Facebook pages and messages that you send us directly through those services.
    * **Third-Party Social Networking Sites.** When you have enabled the use of our Services through a third-party social networking or similar site or mobile or other application (a "Social Networking Site"), such as Facebook, Google+ ,Twitter, or VK you permit Elena’s Models to access certain information about you that is made available to Elena’s Models through or from that Social Networking Site. The information obtained by Elena’s Models varies by Social Networking Site and may be affected by the privacy settings you establish at that Social Networking Site, but can include information such as your name, profile picture, gender, age range or birthday, language, location, country and interests. Elena’s Models will not post anything to your Social networking page.
  5. ## Communications 

Registering for our Services, you consent to receive email messages from us. You can opt out of receiving certain messages from us by visiting the "settings" page of your account or by clicking the “unsubscribe” on these email communications from Elena’s Models. Note that you are not permitted to unsubscribe or opt out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as technical notices or purchase confirmations, or our ongoing business activities in order to provide the Services to you.

  6. ## Security Or Transfer Of Information 

The personal information we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in the Hong Kong and other countries. The countries your personal information is transferred to may not provide the same level of protection as the country you are resident in. Elena’s Models will take reasonable measures to help protect your information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction and to treat it in accordance with this Policy. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We urge you to keep your personal information safe (including your account password). 

  7. ## Order 

Elena's Models do not process credit cards itself, and use a third party service for all payments. Secure transactions are served by Checkout.com - a reliable provider of online credit card payment facilities for thousands of Internet businesses of different trades. Your contact details and credit card details that are necessary for billing purposes are provided by you at a separate website via a secure server. Elena’s Models or any of its companies never holds any credit card details. All transactions are made via secure payments systems provided by Checkout.com. 

Your credit card will be billed by Elena’s Models (Great Media Limited)

  8. ## Cookies 

The types of cookies used on most websites can generally be put into one of the following categories: strictly necessary, analytics, functionality, advertising. In order to provide you with the best browsing experience, Elena’s Models uses those mentioned. You can find out more about the cookies we use from each of the categories below 

    * Strictly Necessary Cookies, essential to make our website work. They enable you to move around our site and use its features. Without these cookies, services that are necessary for you to be able to use the site such as accessing secure areas can't be provided. 
    * Analytics Cookies collect information about how people are using our website. These cookies don't gather information that identifies you and are an anonymous basis 
    * Functionality Cookies, remember choices you make to provide enhanced features and content to you. For example, these cookies can be used to remember your username 
  9. ## Log Files 

We use IP addresses to administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

  10. ## Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Elena's Models are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to the information collected by Elena's Models' web site. 

  11. ## Updates To This Policy 

We reserve the right to modify this Policy from time to time. If we make changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Revision" date below and will post the updated Policy on this page. We may also provide other methods of notice or request your consent depending on the circumstances. 

  12. ## Last Revision Date 

This Policy was last revised on October 7, 2015 

  13. ## Contacting Elenas Models

If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at  
[helpdesk@elenasmodels.com](mailto:helpdesk@elenasmodels.com) or by writing to us at: Great Media Limited , Unit505, 5Flr, Wing On House , 71 Des Veoux Rd, Central, Hong Kong
